Viviana Paola Moreno Rangel



phone number: +64 2041661693

+57 3196952635

email: psrangel.6@gmail.com

About me

I am a psychologist specializing in Social Psychology. I have experience and knowledge in different areas such as legal and social psychology, human rights, training processes and support in territories, areas of technology, and projects with a gender focus.

Qualifications

- 2014 Psychologist. Universidad Católica de Colombia.
- 2017 Specialist in social psychology, cooperation, and community management. Universidad El Bosque.
- Languages:

Spanish: Native.

English: Intermediate.

Experience

Banco Finandina Frontend developer (2022-2023)

Participation in QA processes for managing and organizing development teams, aligned with project requirements, and maintaining the Bank's digital portals.

Comisaria de Familia. Secretaría Distrital de Integración Social Psychologist (2020-2022)

Specialized guidance on the competencies, procedures, and decisive actions for caring for individuals in situations of domestic violence within the current legal framework.

Comisaria de Familia. Secretaría Distrital de Integración Social Psychologist (2018-2019)

Follow-up on cases of domestic violence, child abuse, and sexual violence towards children and adolescents at the Family Police Stations.

Secretaría Distrital de Integración Social Psychologist (2017 - 2018)

Monitoring and support for families and caregivers to ensure the rights of pregnant women and early childhood.

Skills

- Knowledge of human rights.
- Gender approach and violence prevention
- IT/office tools.
- Ability to work independently, creatively, and as a proactive team player.

Fundación Natura ONG Psychologist (2015-2016)

Supporting the selection processes and implementing plans and activities to enhance emotional, social, and occupational well-being, thus improving the workers' quality of life.

- Strong customer service skills with a positive interpersonal approach.
- Languages:

Spanish: Native.

English: Intermediate.

Other qualifications

- Psychological first aid for leaders (2023)
- Project Management for Effective Communication (2023)
- Leadership strategies for women (2021)
- Manager of protective environments and safe territories (2017)
- Promotion, protection, support, and defense of Breastfeeding (2017)